#### Contact

+447448174058 (Mobile) rc.ravulapati@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ravichandrar (LinkedIn)

ravichandra.me/ (Portfolio) jsonformatter.ravichandra.me/ (Other)

ravichandrar.medium.com/ (Blog)

## Top Skills

**JavaScript** 

**TypeScript** 

angular

### Languages

Tamil (Elementary)

English (Professional Working)

Hindi (Native or Bilingual)

Telugu (Native or Bilingual)

### Certifications

Code Jam 2021

Code Jam 2016

Code Jam 2019

**JavaScript** 

Angular

# Ravi Chandra Ravulapati

Vice President at Morgan Stanley | Senior Web Developer | Front End Architect | JavaScript | TypeScript | Angular | Elm

London, England, United Kingdom

## Summary

Over 13 years of developing web and mobile applications using HTML5, JavaScript, JavaScript libraries (Angular, Jquery), J2EE, NodeJS.

Over 12 years of experience in CSS3, CSS Pre-processors (LESS, SCSS) to customize the look and feel of both web and mobile applications.

Over 11 years of experience in developing cross browser compatible web applications (Gracefully degrading the HTML5 features using Modernizr java script library).

Over 10 years of experience in TDD, Test automation and DevOps.

# Experience

Morgan Stanley
Vice President
October 2022 - Present (1 year 5 months)
London, England, United Kingdom

Featurespace
Senior Engineer 2
August 2021 - November 2022 (1 year 4 months)
Cambridge, England, United Kingdom

Tata Consultancy Services
10 years 7 months

Assistant Consultant
December 2016 - September 2021 (4 years 10 months)
London, United Kingdom

IT Analyst

November 2015 - November 2016 (1 year 1 month)

London, United Kingdom

Architecture, development, implementation and Research

Systems Engineering

March 2011 - October 2015 (4 years 8 months)

Chennai Area, India

Architecture, development, implementation and Research

## Education

Gudlavalleru Engineering College

Bachelor of Technology (B.Tech.), Electronics and Communications Engineering · (2005 - 2009)

Satya Junior College

10 + 2, Maths , Physics , Chemistry · (2003 - 2005)

C.P.M High School

10, High School/Secondary Diplomas and Certificates · (2002 - 2003)